{"data":[{"question":"There was a strong smell and the sound of frying. Obviously Mrs.Jones __________ (cook) fish.","a":"was cooking","b":"were cooking","c":"was cookying","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"The director didn't allow the actors to travel by air while they _______ (work) on the film.","a":"was working","b":"were working","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"7"},{"question":"Two men _______ (fight) at a street comer and a policeman _______ (try) to stop them.","a":"were fighting\/were trying","b":"were fighting\/was tring","c":"was fighting\/were trying","d":"were fighting\/was trying","answer":"4","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"The exam had just begun and the candidates _______ (write) their names at the top of their papers.","a":"were writing","b":"was writing","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"7"},{"question":"He said that he was the captain of a ship which _______ (sail) that night for Marseilles.","a":"were sailing","b":"was sailing","answer":"2","explain":"- sail -> sailing.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"7"},{"question":"As she _______ (climb) the ladder it slipped sideways and she fell off it.","a":"were climbing","b":"was climbing","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"7"},{"question":"They had taken off the wheel of the car and _______ (mend) the puncture. I asked when it would be ready.","a":"were mending","b":"was mending","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past (they were mending...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"7"},{"question":"The airplane in which the football team _______ (travel) crashed soon after taking off.","a":"was traveling","b":"was travelling","c":"were traveling","d":"were travelling","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"My wife and I _______ (talk) about you the other day.","a":"was talking","b":"were talking","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"7"},{"question":"Where he _______ (live) when you saw him last?","a":"was he living","b":"were he living","c":"was he liveing","d":"were he liveing","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"}]}